# **TAURIAN GRAHAM**

#### **ABOUT ME**

Full stack developer with experience as a Tech Architecture Delivery Analyst and Software Development. My focus has been developing web applications and restful API's that utilize agile workflows for project management. This while leveraging my Computer Programming background in Game Design & Development from Rochester Institute of Technology.

#### **KEY COURSES**

- Data Structures & Algorithmic Simulations 1 & 2 (C++/OpenGL)
- Web Implementations & Rich Media Web App Dev I,II (HTML/CSS/JS/NodeJS)
- Math Graphical Simulation 1 & 2, AND Interactive Media Development

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Tech Architecture Delivery Analyst | Accenture

Apr. 2022 to Nov. 2023 | Hartford, CT | Full Time

- Analyzed business processes and models to assess future state solutions within the Pharmaceutical and Utilities Retail Industry.
- Utilized Java, Spring Boot, and AWS through application development opportunities.
- Trained in Salesforce Administration/Einstein GPT, Amazon Web Services (Lambda, EC2, VPC, SNS, IAM), and MongoDB.

## IT Manager | White House Liquor

Oct. 2019 to Dec. 2021 | Rochester, NY | Part Time

- Helped implement and currently manage an e-commerce portal, utilizing multiple web API's.
- Improved SQL database to facilitate vendor management.

#### **Customer Delivery | Mastercard**

Jun. 2019 to Aug. 2019 | O'Fallon, MO | Intern

 Enhanced Voice of the Customer Questionnaire process utilizing Microsoft Excel macros to create a standardized model.

## **PROJECTS**

## **Ecommerce Shop (Ongoing) - (JavaScript)**

**Frameworks**: React, SanityIO, MongoDB, Stripe | **System**: Browser Developing a restful ecommerce shop in ReactJS. This microservice is M.E.R.N. based and uses SanityIO & Stripe for product schemas and payment processing.

#### Dungeon Roques (Ongoing) - (C#)

Game Engine: Unity3D | System: Windows

Creating a 3D rogue-like platformer dungeon crawler game in Unity. Play as a dungeon excavator, battling various monsters throughout multiple floors of various themed dungeons.

## Spring Boot Swagger (Completed) - (Java)

**Frameworks**: Spring Boot, SwaggerUI, MongoDB | **System**: Browser Developed a Demo Spring Boot and SwaggerUI project positioned for AWS deployment to post and retrieve user data from MongoDB.

#### **EDUCATION**

Rochester Institute of Technology Rochester, NY Graduated, Dec. 2021

Website: tgramz.xyz Location: Charlotte, NC Email: tfire09@gmail.com Phone: (914)-319-8735

#### **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

- Javascript
- HTML/CSS
- Typescript
- PHP
- C#
- C++
- Xamarin
- Python
- Java

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

- MongoDB
- Maui/Blazor
- SanityIO
- NextJsReactJs
- Spring Boot
- SwaggerUI

#### SOFTWARE/SERVICES

- Microsoft 365
- Visual Studio/VC Code
- Unity3D
- Altassian Jira
- AWS Lamda, EC2, VPC, SNS, IAM

## **SKILLS**

- Object Oriented Programming
- SDLC
- CI/CD
- Restful API's / Microservices
- Project Management
- Troubleshooting
- Business Process Analysis/Design
- Requirement Analysis
- Business Model Strategy

#### **TRAINING**

- Salesforce Administration/Einstein GPT
- AWS Lamda, EC2, VPC, SNS, IAM
- System Integration Testing (SIT)
- Cloud Architecture/Infrastructure
- Testing & Automation

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Triscentis Tosca Automation Specialist Level 1 Sept 14th, 2022
- Coursera Google Python Jul 6th, 2022
- ONLC Introduction to Java Jul 28th, 2017

- Business Analyst
- MongoDB
- Docker
- Kanban
- Agile Workflow